A lot of word,
很多时候
I've been focusing on when I teach Machine Learning,
当我讲授机器学习课程时
as you know training,
都是侧重于
and defining these models.
训练和定义模型
But there's a big other piece,
但是还有其他很重要的环节
and I hear a lot from industry professionals,
我经常听到行业专业人士说
that building is probably the smallest piece of these technologies,
构建模型或许是这些技术中比重最小的环节
like the biggest part is really, maintaining,
最大的环节是根据新收集的数据
updating in the face of gathering new data.
维护和更新模型
So I was wondering if you could speak to what makes Sagemaker and Cloud services,
请介绍下为何掌握 Sagemaker 和云服务技能
a good skill to have career right,
对于职业发展很有用
why is for people who are looking to become machine learning engineer's.
为何想要成为机器学习工程师要掌握这些技能
Okay, let's follow through
我们来看看
the process of building a machine learning product for example.
构建机器学习产品的流程
As you know that involves big data,
机器学习会用到大数据
that involves handling data,
需要处理数据
that involves getting from understanding business problem,
理解商业问题
and mapping that business problem to machine learning problem,
并将商业问题变成机器学习问题
that's already a skill that you are teaching in the program.
你已经在课程中教授这项技能
The other thing that people need to do,
还需要做的是
is to get into collecting the right amount of data,
收集正确数量的数据
that would relate to solve that machine learning problem.
这些数据与解决机器学习问题有关
So there is a data collection,
所以包括数据收集
organization, and analysis component to do there.
整理和分析
Then the next thing that developers and data scientists need to do,
接下来 开发人员和数据科学家需要
is to jump in the process of selecting a machine learning algorithm,
介入并选择机器学习算法
building and training machine learning model from that algorithm,
利用该算法构建和训练机器学习模型
and invalidating that machine learning model against some metrics,
根据某些指标验证机器学习模型
that could be accuracy,
指标包括准确率
that can be cause, that can be time,
成本和时间
and many other parameters that are potentially used to the business.
以及企业会用到的很多其他参数
Then if they have a satisfactory machine learning model
如果根据所选指标判断
based on the metrics that they have,
模型令人满意
then they can put that in production.
那么可以将模型部署到生产环境中
If they don't have a satisfactory model,
如果对模型不满意
then it goes back in the process of collecting the data,
则重新收集数据
or selecting different algorithms.
或选择不同的算法
So if you think about that entire end to end process of machine learning,
这就是整个端到端机器学习流程
as learners are going through the process of learning
学员会学习
how to apply that process to the data,
如何将这一流程应用到数据上
companies are also going through the process
企业也会经历
of automating that machine learning life-cycle.
自动化这个机器学习生命周期的流程
So there's synergy there,
这就存在协同效果
where as a learner,
作为学员
it's very important for you to get acquainted with a tool
熟悉一款能帮助你掌握
that can teach you the best practices involved in that process,
机器学习流程涉及的最佳做法的工具非常重要
and Sagemaker does that.
Sagemaker 就是这样的工具
Sagemaker would facilitate the process of collecting data,
Sagemaker 可以帮助你收集数据
and in the platform will essentially instruct you
并告诉你哪些是
as what are the best ways to look at data labeling practices,
查看数据标记做法的最佳方式
and then understand how to handle over the data to a machine learning algorithm or model.
然后了解如何将数据提供给机器学习算法或模型
Then when it comes to training machine learning algorithms at scale,
在大规模地训练机器学习算法时
the platform is designed with APIs and all other related automation,
Sagemaker 提供了 API 和其他相关的自动化功能
to essentially create clusters,
可以创建聚类
apply hyper-parameter optimization in some cases to the algorithms, such as training,
在训练等过程中对算法进行超参数优化
and give you some validation metrics for you to look at,
并提供一些验证指标
whether your machine learning algorithm was a successful trained algorithm or not.
使你能够判断机器学习算法是否是训练成功的算法
Then the next thing that is possible to do with the platform is,
接下来 Sagemaker 还可以
automate the deployment of the machine learning model in production.
自动将机器学习模型部署到生产环境中
So again, following the process of
整个流程就是
building and training and deploying machine-learning algorithms.
构建 训练和部署机器学习算法
So if you get into that mindset,
如果你掌握了这个流程
you stand much more like a higher probability of
在应聘机器学习类岗位时
being successful in an interview with an employer,
你更有可能
that is interested in machine learning,
应聘成功
because they are going through the exact same process.
因为他们也会经历相同的流程
Yeah, the great thing about machine learning is that,
机器学习的精彩之处是
these algorithms improve over time with more data and more examples.
在获得越来越多的数据和样本后 算法将逐渐改进
When do you think about developing a product,
在开发产品时
it's very different than something that's
与让某人实际完成的任务
just a physical thing that you get someone has done,
截然不同
is something that you want to be able to go through this cycle of gathering data,
你希望能够经历收集数据和改进算法的循环过程
improving your algorithm, I think it can be the best thing to your consumers.
然后向消费者呈现最好的产品
So really thinking about that whole cycle,
想想这整个过程
when you're a part of a team,
你是团队的一员
or an engineer who's in charge of all of that,
或者是一名负责所有这些的工程师
it is really important.
这很重要
So I'm excited to be partner with you and teach all these things.
非常激动能够与你合作讲授这些课程